Ever wonder why you can feel okay right
after a concussion… and then feel terrible
later?
That's because a concussion doesn't always
cause something you can see from the
outside.
After an injury, the brain can temporarily
have trouble communicating efficiently and
managing the energy it needs to function
normally.
That can affect everything from
concentration and memory to balance,
energy, and how you process information.
And symptoms can fluctuate.
You might feel pretty good one day and
struggle the next.
Sometimes, too much physical or mental
activity can temporarily make symptoms
worse. That doesn't necessarily mean
you're getting new brain damage—
it can mean your brain needs a little more
time and the right recovery strategy.
If your symptoms are sticking around,
don't just push through them.
Get evaluated and find out what your brain
needs.